Guide to the North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs, Student Media Authority Records
North Carolina State University, Division of Student Affairs, Student Media Authority Records
- Negatives, Contact sheets, and Slides, 1987-2003; 1987 2003
  - Negatives, 1991-2003
    - John Stogner - Service Raleigh, Stroud Center, Student Computer Use, Student Government Election [includes 1 sheet of slides], 1998-2001 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Josh A., 2002 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Josh Michel [mostly slides], 2003 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Justin W. - Student Presidential Candidates, undated (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - Karen Hill, 2003 (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - Kim - Athletics, Career Fair, Experiment, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Kyle Hall - Soccer, other campus shots, 1998-1999 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Lane Jessup - Athletics, Centennial Campus, Counties, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Lane Jessup - Athletics, Fair, Job Fair, Take Back the Night, other campus shots, 2000-2001 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Latoya - Career Fair, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Lauren - Concert, Volleyball, 2001 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Lee Ann van Leer, undated (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Linda Tuttle - Features, Al Farrow sculpture, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Lindsay McDonald, 2002-2003 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Mana Yagani [professionally developed negatives], 2002 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Marty - Athletics, Library Preservation, Memphis, Student Organizations, Take Back the Night, 1997-1998 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Mary - Athletics, Craft Fair, School of Design, 1998, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Matt Huffman - Athletics, Lecture on Cosmology, 2002 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Meng - Athletics, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Meng - Athletics, Design School, 1999-2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Milton - AACC, Hillsborough Street, Shack-a-thon, undated (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Moses - Athletics, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Natalie - Athletics, First Roll, International Festival, Provost, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Neil Saunders - Athletics, 1998 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Nina Desai - Cake Walk, 25 February (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Pete Ellis [includes 2 sheets of slides], 2003 (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Peter - Football, 1999 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Pittman - CHASS, PAMS, Textiles, and Engineering Deans; Buildings, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Rachel Martin, 2001-2002 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Ratna Adhar - Vothing, Feature, Soccer, 2000-2001 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Rob Bradley (1 of 2), 2003-2004 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Rob Bradley (2 of 2) [includes slides], 2003-2003 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Rob Peterson - Alumni Meeting, Art Complexes, Athletics, Features, 1998-1999 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - Rob Peterson - Soccer, Dr. Beremon, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Robert - Akido Club, Athletics, Career Fair, PAMS, 1999-2000 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - Robert - Athletics, undated (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Robert - Stories, Women's Soccer, 1999 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Ron Hunter - Baseball, Football, Volleyball, Wrestling, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Ron Hunter - Jimmy V Golf, Leaders of the Pack, Self Defense, Special Olympics, other campus shots (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Ron Hunter - Men's and Women's Soccer, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Tamara Lockhart - Career Fair, State Fair, 1998 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Tasha Petty, 2003 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Theresa - Athletics, Career Fair, NABA Meeting, 2000-2001 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Theresa - Athletics, Fall, School of Design, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - Theresa - College of Engineering, Dare County, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - Tim - Athletics, Jazz Band Concert, 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Tim Goodson, 1999, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Tonya Black - CALS, Career Fair, State Fair, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - WB - Athletics, 2001 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Wortham - Athletics, Fair, 2000 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - Athletics (unlabeled), 1997-2001 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - Athletics (various photographers), 1997-1999 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - Athletics, campus shots, 1998-1999 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - Athletics, campus shots, 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Athletics, campus shots, 1999-2002, undated (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Baseball, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Buildings, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Campus Shots, 1993-2000 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - Campus Shots, 1995-2000 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Campus Shots, 1997-1998 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Campus Shots - made into prints, 1999 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Campus Shots (1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Campus Shots (2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - Concert [professionally developed negatives], 2002? (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Concert [professionally developed photos], 2002? (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Cross Country and Track, 1997-1998 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Davie County, NC [professionally developed negatives], undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Davie County, NC [professionally developed photos] (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Features, 1995-2001 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Football, 1995-1999, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - FSU Sports, 1998-1999 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - Gymnastics, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Hockey, 2000 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Men's Basketball, undated (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Men's Basketball, 1999-2000 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Men's Soccer, 1996-2001 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - New Photos [negatives], September - October 2003 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - News Shots, 1995-1996 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Scanned Collages, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Students, campus [unlabeled photographs], undated (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Swimming, 1999-2000 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Tennis, 1997-1999, undated (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Volleyball, 1997-1999, undated (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Women's Basketball, 1996-2000, undated (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Women's Soccer, 1999-2000 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Contact Sheets, 1987-2001
    - AB - Assembly, Classrooms, Dogs, various campus shots, 1999, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Angela - Athletics, Romeo and Juliet, Washington DC, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Ashley Britt - Hurricane Floyd, campus events, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Crystal - Athletics; Curris - Ladies in Red, 2001 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Dan - Athletics, 1998-1999 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Dave - Bricks, 1998 (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Erica Tuers - Athletics, various campus events, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Gigi Cheung - Men's and Women's Basketball, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Gigi Cheung - Athletics, Blood Drive, College, Crossroads, Washington DC, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Iyare - Hurricane Floyd, Yellow Man, 1999 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Iyare - Athletics, City Streets, Franklin Street Halloween, 1999-2000 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Jamie - Athletics, Graduation, Snow, other campus shots, 1998-2000 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Jamie - Baseball, Play, March 1999 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Jana - Athletics, CALS, Dog Olympics, 2000-2001 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - Jana - Baseball, Basketball, Football, Fair, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Jeff - Athletics, Skyline, 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Jen James - Madrigal Dinner, Vet School, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Jessica - Volleyball, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Joey Luther - Athletics, Fair, Election, Protest, New Athletic Director, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Joey Luther - Athletics, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - John - Athletics, Construction, Counties, Student Government Election, other campus shots, 1999-2001 (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Kim - Athletics, Career Fair, undated (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Kyle - Design School, Soccer, other campus shots, 1998-1999 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Lane Jessup - Athletics, Counties, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - Lane Jessup - Athletics, Fair, Job Fair, Surrey/Stokes, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - Latoya - Career Fair, 2000 (Box 36, Folder 12)
    - Lee Ann van Leer - Campus and Dorm Shots, April 1987 (Box 36, Folder 13)
    - Marty - Athletics, other campus shots, 1997 (Box 36, Folder 14)
    - Mary - Athletics, Craft Fair, other campus shots, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 15)
    - Meng - Football, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 16)
    - Meng - Athletics, Concert, Costumes, 1999-2000 (Box 36, Folder 17)
    - Moses - Athletics, Concert, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 18)
    - Natalie - Athletics, International Festival, Provost, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 19)
    - Neil - Men's Basketball vs. Duke, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 20)
    - Peter - Football, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 21)
    - Robert - Soccer, 1999 (Box 36, Folder 22)
    - Theresa - Athletics, Fall, 2000-2001 (Box 36, Folder 23)
    - Tim - Athletics, 1999-2001 (Box 36, Folder 24)
    - Tonya Black - CALS, Career Fair, State Fair, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 25)
    - WB - Athletics, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 26)
    - Wortham - Athletics, 2001 (Box 36, Folder 27)
    - Athletics, 1997-2001 (Box 36, Folder 28)
    - Athletics, 1999-2001 (Box 36, Folder 29)
    - Band, Theater, other campus shots, February-April 1999 (Box 36, Folder 30)
    - Baseball, March-May 1999 (Box 36, Folder 31)
    - Baseball, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Campus Shots, 1999 (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - Campus Shots, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - Campus Shots, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Canon EOS Systems Photography Book and Notes, undated (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - Cross Country, Soccer, Volleyball, October-May 1998 (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - Dancing with Wolves, Madrigal Dinner, other campus shots, December 1999-March 2000 (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Football, October-December 1998 (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - Football, 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - Football - Bowl Game, January 1999 (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - Football, November 1999 (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Graduation, other campus shots, 1997-2000 (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - Gymnastics, 2000-2001 (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - Headshots, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
    - Hockey, 2000 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Jimmy V Golf Tournament - Kay Yow, Michael Jordan, September 1999 (Box 37, Folder 16)
    - Management and Textiles Buildings, other campus shots, February-April 1999 (Box 37, Folder 17)
    - Martial Arts, Rugby, Student Performances, Springtime Campus Shots, February-May 1999 (Box 37, Folder 18)
    - Men's Basketball (1 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 19)
    - Men's Basketball (2 of 2), 1998-2000 (Box 37, Folder 20)
    - Men's Soccer, 1999-2000 (Box 37, Folder 21)
    - Newspaper Clippings (photography), 1998 (Box 37, Folder 22)
    - Protest/Rally, undated (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Rock Climbing, March 2000 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Snow, Career Fair, other campus shots, December 1999-April 2000 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - State Fair, other campus shots, September-December 1999 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - State Fair, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Student and Faculty Meetings/Assemblies, November 1998-April 1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - WKNC 'Natural Healing Band,' Dorm and Classroom shots, February-May 1999 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Women's Basketball, 1998-2000 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Women's Basketball, 1999-2001 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Women's Soccer, 1999-2000 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Wrestling, 1998-2000 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Slides, 1987-2001
    - Athletics, Campus Shots, 1987, undated (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Brent Road the day after - Liz, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Calendar Cover, August 1993 (Cardbox 40)
    - Campus, Fair, Student Events, undated (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Campus Cover, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Campus Cover, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Centennial Campus, 11 November 1995 (Cardbox 40)
    - Christmas Slide Show, 1992 (Cardbox 40)
    - D.C., November 1995 (Cardbox 40)
    - Dean of Design, Fair, 2001, undated (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Dorm Security - Liz, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Fair - Aner, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Fair - Ashlea, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Fair - Salvador, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Fall Color - Ashlea G., undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Final Edited, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - First Staff Meeting, Fall 1995 (Cardbox 40)
    - Football Coach - Mike O'Cain, undated (Cardbox 40)
    - Hide - Pumpkins, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - HT, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Mall Home EOS Labs - D. Lockwog, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Mall Home SMA - Liz Mahncke, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Meet the Pack, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - PS, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Random Soccer - Chris Hondros, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - SF, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Tab Shots, 1995 (Cardbox 41)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 41)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
    - Unlabeled box, undated (Cardbox 42)
- Unprocessed Records, 1909-2011
  - Unprocessed Records, 1900s (Carton 8)